(Leonard:)Sheldon, the world is filled
with dirty, discarded socks.
(Sheldon:)Not my world.
(Leonard:)You know who'd really dig
seeing this experiment? Penny.
(Sheldon:)I wasn't aware that lunar ranging
was her thing.
(Sheldon:)Although I suppose...
(Sheldon:)...the retroreflector left on the moon
by Neil Armstrong...
(Sheldon:)...does qualify as a shiny object.
(Raj:)Ask her to come up.
I don't know. It's still weird since,
you know....
(Howard:)-She dumped you?
-She didn't dump me.
(Leonard:)We were just in different places
in the relationship.
(Sheldon:)I fail to see how a relationship...
(Sheldon:)...can have the qualities
of a geographic location.
Well, it's very simple. Leonard was living
in a town called Please Don't Leave Me...
(Howard:)...while Penny had just moved
to the island of Bye-bye.
(Leonard:)Screw you, guys.
I'm gonna go see if she's home.
(Howard:)If it's not too much trouble,
I'd like to point this at the moon now.
(Raj:)Wait a second.
The good wife is crying.
(Raj:)Something's very wrong.